http://www.historicalbricks.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Search for:
(319) 354-5251info@historicalbricks.com
PRIVACY POLICYThis notice discloses our privacy practices. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site while you shop for bricks and pavers online.Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe may have access to and may collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, via the website or your use of the website, or via other direct contact from you. We may use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us, if applicable. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.CookiesWe may use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.Links to Other WebsitesThis web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Google Analytics FeaturesThis site has implemented Google Analytics for Display Advertising, in order to advertise online (which we do) via its “Remarketing” feature. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website.Vistors can opt-out of Google’s use of Cookies and also Google Analytics for Display Advertising by using the Ads Settings found here: https://www.google.com/settings/adsVisitors can opt-out of Google Remarketing campaigns by using the Doubleclick opt-out page here:https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout To unsubscribe from our email list please contact us at michelle@historicalbricks.com Get StartedRequest a quote or call us now at (319) 354-5251 to discuss your projectRequest A Quote
